OK. We need it, brother.
Come on everybody.
Oh, yeah brothers, sisters.
Friends!
One, two. One, two, three, four.
I hope that you come over tonight and give me your hands.
Listen closely, my love.
I need you to come over today and feel my heart.
Feel how it beats.
How it's dying for your warmth.
Feel how it sighs, how it's dying from that pain.
Come on, let's go. Come and heal my soul.
Come. Let's go. Come and heal my heart.
I want you to come and bare that body.
I want you to come and bare this soul.
To have you here in my arms.
Man. To see you again and make love to you.
I need your warmth, I'm dying for your love, baby.
I need your warmth. I'm dying for your love, baby.
I need your warmth, I'm dying for your love.
I need.
Hey, play, stop.
OK. It's getting a little hot in here, right?
I don't understand how I've spent so much time being so hooked.
Hey, no. I can't understand how I don't, I don't stop loving you.
Don't be a fucking asshole.
A series of outbursts that always shatters my sanity.
Pure adrenaline. It's a sweet, terrible thing.
Come on, let's go. Come and fix my soul.
Hey. Come on, let's go. Come and fix my heart.
I need you to undress that body.
I need you to bare this soul.
To hold you here in my arms.
To see you again and make love to you.
I need your warmth, I'm dying for your love.
I need your warmth, I'm dying for your love, baby.
I need your warmth.
I'm dying for your love, baby.
I need your warmth, I need it.
Everybody put your hands together with me like this.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
I need your warmth.
I need your warmth, I'm dying for your love.
I need it.
Thank you.
Thanks a lot. Oh, my God, we are so very excited to be here.
We are so very happy. And so thrilled.
You know, it's like after thirty years playing together and doing tours around the world.
It's very exciting to be here with you guys.
So, thank you for coming.
We are Panteón Rococó representing Mexico City.
The big — yeah — the big fucking monster Mexico City.
So this one, this song is called, it's called "1993..." and it's dedicated to all the missing people all around Mexico.
The morning that you left.
My life went out the window.
I search for your body day and night, down the avenue and through the memories.
I want to tell you that I still wait for you, sitting on the railing of my window.
And even though piercing silence of the night viciously wrecks my hope.
So it is.
The uncertainty of not having you with me robs me of my breath.
It clips my wings, your absence hurts me and deep down it wounds and lacerates my existence.
It hurts to remember you in the house.
They hurt, the meaningless words hurt.
They hurt, memories of you in the house hurt.
The words hurt.
That's right. Mexico, stand up.
Mexico resists with strength, with dignity, with non-violence.
Let's go.
I will not stop looking for you, my love.
Someone suddenly stole all my joy.
I turn on a light for your soul and your smile.
The morning you left, my life went out the window.
I look for your body day and night, down the avenue and through memories.
I want to tell you that I'm still waiting for you, sitting by the railing of my window.
And even though the silence of the piercing night viciously wounds my hope.
My hope.
Listen to this, for all our disappeared back in Mexico.
I miss you. I always look for you.
Someday we will meet again.
Right here. Right now.
Look at us, where we have ended up.
Think about it. We shouldn't have let it pass us by.
Come, sit down. Let's talk for a while.
And then maybe it will be time to end it and find a way out of this bottomless pit.
I know it hurts us and wounds us deeply.
And what can I say to you? How do I explain it to you?
How do I tell you that it will be hard to not see you anymore.
Habit has already taken hold of us and the love we felt for each other.
It has slipped away, it has fallen apart, it is so broken that it will be hard to heal.
Hey, look at yourself.
Are you crying again?
Listen to me.
I'm sorry I made you cry.
But tell me. (Tell me.) How long have we been like this?
And then maybe we can let each other go.
And look for a way out of this bottomless pit.
I know it hurts us and cuts us deeply, and what do I tell you?
How do I explain it to you? How do I tell you that it will be hard to not see you anymore.
But habit has already gotten the best of us and the love we felt for each other.
Has vanished, has fallen apart, it is so broken that it will be hard to heal.
No! Not seeing you anymore, my love.
Not seeing you anymore.
Not seeing you anymore, never seeing you ever again anymore.
Cha-cha love. Cha-cha love.
Finding the way out of this bottomless pit.
I know that it hurts us and cuts us deeply.
And what do I tell you? How do I explain it to you?
How do I tell you that it will be hard to not see you anymore.
But I've gotten used to it.
It took hold of us, and the love we felt for each other has vanished.
It has fallen apart. It is so broken that it will be hard to mend.
Yeah. Thank you, guys. Thank you. Thanks a lot.
OK, papi.
OK. Play it. Hey.
Right there. Just right there.
We continue broadcasting directly from National Public Radio for you.
Directly, directly Washington, D.C., baby.
This is Panteón Rococó with flavor, with groove.
Today with ease. Play it, my boy, sound like this, sound like this, papa.
And after tearing the sky apart together, right there, just like that.
In your special way of making love and exploding when you come.
No, I cannot accept that you are leaving today.
You owe me a quarter of a thousand battles.
And I do not want to charge, I just want you to stay here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Today you leave.
But I know you will come back. That what I gave you, you will never find again.
Those nights and those days, when you writhed in my arms.
When we watched stars, and you were one of them, one of those that embrace the earth with their light.
And today you call me and tell me that you are packing up your life.
And that you have packed your bags and today you say goodbye.
And after breaking the sky together, oh, with that unique you have of making love.
And exploding upon coming, I can't accept that you're leaving today.
You owe me a quarter of a thousand battles.
And charging, I don't want to. No, I don't want to charge.
I just want you to stay here.
Today my body needs you.
Knowing that the perfect dose is in your hips.
In your kisses, your smile, your hair, and that body that gives me chills.
Today my soul knows you are fine.
But you, you, you tell me who will be there to soothe my pain if you're no longer here.
Play it.
And after tearing through the sky together, with that unique way you make love.
And exploding, upon coming, I can't accept that you're leaving today.
You owe me quarter of a thousand battles.
And I don't want to charge, I don't want to collect.
I just want you to stay here.
Today my body needs you.
Knowing that the perfect dose is in your hips.
In your kisses, your smile, your hair, and that body that gives me chills.
Today my soul knows you are fine.
But you, you, you tell me who will be there to soothe my pain if you're no longer here?
Ready. Let's do the skanking! One, two, one, two, three.
Today my body needs you.
Knowing that the perfect dose is in your hips, in your kisses, your smile, your hair, and that body that gives me chills.
Today my soul knows that you're okay.
But you, you, you tell me who will be there to soothe.
To soothe.
Sing it!
Oh, my soul knows that you're OK.
But you, you tell me what.
OK, thank you very much. Play it.
Play it. Say it for the whole world.
For everybody. Poor people have no place.
Go!
In the morning, I wake up, I don't feel like going to work.
I get on the bus and watch as all the people start walking along the avenue.
The working-class soul of my city.
People who are always working and use their rest to dream.
To dream!
Gentleman, ladies.
After eight hours of working, hopelessness is felt at home.
Because with the daily grind I endure, it's no longer enough to make it.
And so dozens of years have passed.
Because in a globalized world
poor people have no place.
Because in the globalized world
Play it, say it.
And scarcity? (Up.) Or wages. (Down.)
What I make at that company isn't enough to feed myself.
And scarcity. (Up.) Or wages. (Down.)
And I tell my Teresa I'm not going to give up.
And scarcity. (Up.) Or wages. (Down.) With what I make at that company it isn't enough to buy food.
And scarcity. (Up.) Or wages. (Down.) And I tell my Teresa, come on, let's dance.
Because. (Here comes.) Who's coming? (Here comes.) Who's coming? (Here comes.)
Come! (Here comes.) Who's coming? (Here comes.) Who's coming? (Here comes.)
Who's coming? (Here comes.) No! (Here comes!) No! (Here comes.)
Here comes the chili that supports you, and entertains you in bed, and in your mouth you hold it.
Better bring your partner and blow in her ear so she moves her hips and gets hot.
And after the rubbing, she won't want anything else.
And tells you no, no, no, no, no, no.
No!
Let's go.
Hey, it's over.
Wait a minute. Everybody, thanks for being here.
It feels so great to be finally here at the Tiny Desk.
We're so happy.
Thank you so much to everyone watching us.
Thanks for coming. Thank you so much for the support.
See you. Mexico City, papa.
Down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down.
"Nach unten" means down. Means everybody go down, down, down, down, down, down.
Down, down, down, down.
Peace and resistance in the world forever.
Enjoy the silence. Down, down. The time is right here, right now. OK, here we go.
Everybody. How do you feel?
OK. Up. Up. Up. Up. Up. Up.
Up. Up. Up. Up. Up. Up.
Oh, my God! Jump! Jump! Jump! Jump! Jump!
Tiny Desk!
The Tiny little Desk.
Brother. Representing Mexico City.
Very proud, very powerful.
Everybody, thank you very much.
Oh, olé, olé, olé. Panteón, Panteón.
Thank you.